beingindian.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Being Indian

##### Thank you for visiting our website. **The Aleph Group PTE Limited** (“ **Aleph** ”) and its Affiliates own and operate this website.  In this terms of use guide, we refer to all of the companies in our corporate group as “ **Aleph** “, “ **we** “, “ **our** ” or “ **us** “. References to “ **you** ”, and “ **your** ” shall be deemed to be references to you accessing this website.

##### The **Privacy Policy** on this website explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used through this website.

##### Aleph respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protect it in all respects.

##### With a view to offer enriching internet experience to its users Aleph offers a vast repository of channels and a variety of services.

##### The information about the user as collected by Aleph is:

##### (a) information supplied by users and  
(b) information automatically tracked while browsing (Information).

##### To avail certain services on our website, users are required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:- a) your name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) PIN code, (f) address etc., and / or your occupation, interests, and the like. The Information as supplied by the users enables us to improve our sites and provide you the most user-friendly experience. For certain services, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. When you send email or other communication to Aleph we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

##### To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use “cookies”, or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user’s individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Newsletter). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control.

##### Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data – such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

##### Aleph may include links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can’t find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site’s homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.

##### We present information to our advertisers — to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website — it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with Aleph, we may contact you from time to time about updation of our content to provide you such features that we believe may benefit you.

##### All information gathered on Aleph is securely stored within the Aleph controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.

##### We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

##### Aleph only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Aleph in the following limited circumstances:

  1. ##### We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information

  2. ##### We provide such information to our persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

##### We will cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, UserID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to Intellectual Property right’s owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

##### Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

##### However the Internet is an ever evolving medium. By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the website. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our privacy policy will be communicated through our Web site at least 10 days in advance of implementation.
